Harper, I need you to
take this seriously.
Do you have any fours?
Freddie, just go fish.
She's waiting to
hear about the job
: With Double Dutch.
Don't say her name!
You'll jinx me.
- Who's Double Dutch?
- What did I just say?
The aforementioned is
an emerging pop star
with a million
Instagram followers.
She's got the blue check.
Oh, so she's not
real world famous,
she's just online famous.
- Hey!
Before you're a household name,
- you're a handheld name.
- Yeah.
And handheld names can have
long and fulfilling careers
dressing up as tacos on their
wildly popular Web shows.
Oh, that reminds me, we're
doing that sketch later.
I got to go pick up my Taco
Tina costume from the cleaners.
Uh, do you need
to borrow my car?
No. I have my own
car, thank you.
- Or you could take mine.
- : I don't have a car,
but I can call you an
ethical rideshare company,
as soon as there is one.
Look, my car is fine.
So what if it goes
when I'm going uphill?
If I have to walk uphill,
I make that noise, too.
It doesn't mean that
there's anything wrong.
Hi, I'm Wes.
Uh, I hope you
didn't wait too long.
I, I would hate for
you to get soggy.
: Oh, this?
It's just for a
silly Internet thing.
I'm Taco Tina.
I'm a taco, but I have all the
same problems as any other girl.
Including car troubles?
Uh, 'cause according
to Quadruple A,
you've called a tow truck nine
times in the last six months.
What? No, I'm sure
it's not that many.
Uh, really? 'Cause you get
the tenth tow for free.
Oh, yeah, you know,
i-it has been nine.
This guy here is Vin Diesel,
'cause he has a VIN number
and he takes diesel.
He takes unleaded.
You haven't been putting
diesel in this car, have you?
No.
Definitely not.
He probably just
needs a new battery.
No, your battery's fine.
But your drum brakes are shot,
you have a failed generator,
and there's a crack
in the engine block.
Oh, is that all?
: Oh, you wish.
You have a fried distributor,
and that air filter is
an environmental hazard.
No, that's fine. I
wiped it off last year.
Trust me. I've been doing
this since I was six,
and I've been fixing Hot
Wheels since I was two.
Okay, but you don't know
how tough Vin Diesel is.
I've had him forever, and
he's always pulled through.
Be honest, you're just
trying to upsell me.
If you want me to be honest,
you might want to think about
getting rid of this old clunker.
The repairs are gonna cost more
than Mr. Diesel's even worth.
Worth? Worth?!
Can you put a price on the
perfect drive-through Coke,
drunk beneath the stars
on a crisp autumn evening?
Yes.
And so can most fast
food restaurants.
Uh, should we just go
back to your place?
: My place?
That's presumptuous.
Your place, as in the
place I'm towing your car.
I presume.
$15,000 to fix a car?
You could get one-third
of a Birkin bag for that.
Purses cost that much?
Great, now you got me
thinking about purses,
which is reminding me of
the styling job with Dutch,
which I'm trying
not to think about.
You brought up the purse!
Oh! So now we're
blaming the victim?
Thank you, Fredward.
I wish there was a way to
know if my car really needed
all that work or if
that mechanic was just
trying to take advantage of me.
You could take a
auto repair class.
I saw a flyer for one at
the community college.
I was there for my
investing class.
: Investing! Great!
Now I'm thinking about
this. Wow, Millicent.
You know, I love this idea.
I can take a car repair
class, fix Vin Diesel,
and then talk
about it on iCarly.
I can't be the only woman who's
sick of condescending mechanics.
Hey, it's not just women.
When I got my oil changed,
it cost an extra $400
to fix my "shock exacerbater."
What's a shock exacerbater?
It is a made-up
thing that cost $400.
Well, they're gonna be naming
made-up auto parts after me
once I ace this class like
Hermione freaking Granger.
Hermione Freaking
Granger was the title
of Dutch's first album!
Come on, Carly!
-  Ah, vino.
The serum of truth.
But we already know
every single thing
there is to know about
each other.
I faked it!
What? Last night?
All of it. The whole time.
Since I've known you?
Since before that.
Guess that makes me feel
a little bit better.
I just couldn't keep lying
to you a moment longer.
Oh, please don't be upset.
I'm more disappointed in myself.
Is there anything I
could've done better?
More wiggling? I-I'm
here to listen.
Spencer, I faked
my own kidnapping.
: Oh, thank God.
It's not me, it's you!
Okay. Why'd you do that?
When our family lost
all of our money,
I was being hounded
by the paparazzi,
bill collectors, the media...
Mostly bill collectors.
So I hopped on a
cruise and sailed away.
Suddenly it's all
like, "kidnapping this"
and "debt forgiveness"
that, so...
Wow.
Now we're even closer
than before! Yay!
You're not mad?
As long as you were never
a rodeo clown, we're fine.
Well, that's great.
Do you think Harper
will understand?
No.  No.
She's gonna kill you
and bury you at sea.
I'll lay fresh
kelp at your grave.
Wow, look at all these women.
And you. And that guy.
A camaraderie of sisterhood,
joining hands to say,
"We can fix it ourselves."
I'm gonna start
taking notes now.
You know where class
starts, Millicent?
In here.
That's your clavicle.
I just can't wait to learn
everything there is
to know about cars.
I truly am a renaissance person.
But most importantly,
I'm gonna get Vin
Diesel in tip-top shape.
MTV Movie Award winner for
Best Tank Top Vin Diesel?
He's in perfect shape.
Oh, my car's name is Vin Diesel.
Yesterday, this guy tried to
charge me $15,000 for repairs.
Ugh, the worst.
But you're gonna love the
instructor of this class.
He is so patient and smart,
and when he shows you
how to do a tune-up,
it's almost... tender.
As long as he's honest.
I just can't take
another skeezy scammer,
like that guy I met yesterday.
Skeezy scammer?
Sounds like a jerk.
Yeah, he sure w... Aah! You.
Hi. Welcome to class, everyone.
Ooh, twinsies.
This is your shop?
Yes. Uh, it was my grandfather's
and then my father's
and now mine.
Cars run in the family.
So you earned none of this.
Oh, Regina.
Hey, it-it's great
to see you again.
If you take this
class any more times,
you're gonna be the
one teaching it.
Can I take a picture of you?
Okay, class, let's go
ahead and get started.
You know, this class is a sham.
You're giving people false hope.
'Cause then, when they realize
they can't fix their own cars,
they're gonna crawl back to you
and then you can swindle them.
It's just like one
of those restaurants
that gives you free chips and
then charges a ton for guac.
Is that one of Taco
Tina's troubles?
That's not what's
happening here, okay?
I-I just like to empower people
so that they don't need
someone like me to come in
and "vansplain."
Vansplain!
No matter how many times I hear
that, it just gets funnier.
Lady, be cool.
First thing I want
to teach you all is
how to monitor your
vehicle's fluids.
So who wants to come up
and help me check the oil?
Please, God, I never
ask for anything.
How about you, Carly?
Fine.
I was just trying to give
someone else a chance,
since I already know
how to do all this,
but I suppose I can demonstrate
for the good of my peers.
Great.
Then reach on down in
and grab the dipstick.
- Seriously?
- I didn't name it.
Not it.
I know. I was just testing you.
Good job. You passed.
Here, let me just help.
Look, I can do it myself.
Okay, class.
Who can tell me what
Carly did wrong?
If this doesn't put
Harper in the right mood
to hear bad news, I
don't know what will.
I snagged the limited edition
Normani Off Balance sneakers
she's been coveting.
You wear them on your hands.
And I got this $2,000
bottle of champagne.
I bought it at an estate sale
of someone who went bankrupt
buying $2,000
bottles of champagne.
And I framed this photo of our
least favorite cousin Roxy.
No matter what I do, I'll always
look better in comparison.
- Go to hell, Roxy.
She's here.
Hold up. Flowers? Bubbly?
Limited edition
Normani Off Balance sneakers!
You wear them on your hands.
You two did all this for me?
We did, because we love you,
and we need to tell you...
How happy you are that I got the
styling job with Double Dutch?
Wait. How did
you two already hear?
: You got the job?
You got the job!
Oh! There's even
a picture of Roxy,
to remind me that I'm
doing better than her.
My L-F-C-U-M-E-B-M.
L-F-C-U-M-E-B-M?
Least favorite cousin unless
Maeve ever betrays me.
Back from the dumb
auto mechanic class
that I'm never going back to.
Flowers? Bubbly?
Normani Off Balance sneakers
that you wear on your hands?
- You got the job! Oh, my God!
-  Yes! Come here!
Oh, yay!
Yeah, yeah. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Now that we're all
in such a good mood,
Maeve has something
she'd like to say.
Harper, I just want you to know.
I am so happy for you!
Oh, you know what we need?
A champagne shower.
No, no, no! That bottle
cost more than my...
Oh, I actually have
a strategy meeting
with Double Dutch in the studio,
so I can't celebrate right now.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah. That's smart.
Who do we think we
are, the Chicago Bulls?
- So, no champy shou shou?
Oh, no, go ahead, just
don't get any on me.
Oh, yeah, do Spencer.
- Yas!
New plan.
We never tell Harper
I faked my kidnapping.
I don't want to be the new Roxy.
Fantastic. We go on
happily living our lives.
You and I in romantic bliss,
and Harper working her
dream job with Double Dutch.
- Are you...?
- Double Dutch?
The singer/producer/cult icon,
once described by Pitchfork as
"the most innovative
star to be born
in the year 1994."
No shade to Bieber,
but where is the lie?
Yes. C'est moi.
In the flesh.
I'm here for my strategy
meeting with Harper.
I guess, uh, on-the-rise
pop stars don't knock.
We don't.
But tell me about
this fake kidnapping.
And use a three-act structure,
a proper hero's
journey, if you will.
Uh, or, or
how about none of us speak
a word about the kidnapping?
Oh, I won't speak a word.
Okay.
But I do love to sing.
Okay, plan A,
I somehow keep Double Dutch
from spilling the beans.
Oh, well, then what's plan B?
We go to Honduras
under the names Terrence
and Felicity Tacoma.
We settle in the small
town of La Esperanza.
We grow peaches
and teach basket-weaving
to the children.
I like peaches, but
let's start with plan A.
I don't trust that Wes, and
I don't need that class.
I already have the greatest
teacher in the world:
The Internet.
If I can install
my own ceiling fan,
I can tune up my car.
Great idea, Carly.
I'm sure a 30-second TikTok
can fix this death trap.
Millicent might have a point.
Freddie, just hand me
that, uh, twisty thingy.
- Okay. This is no big deal.
- All right.
- No! Ah. No.
- Whoa. Hey! I got you!
- Come on.
- Son of a...!
You know what? That's okay.
I've almost got it.
Freddie, go check
the spark plugs.
- All right.
- Millicent, start him up!
- Oh!
Millicent, stop that!
Then you two stop cussing.
Ooh!
Okay. I've got it.
Wow. Should I start
my own auto shop?
No, no, no, no!
Vin Diesel, are you okay?
Carly, you need to
call a real mechanic.
- Never in a million...
- Hand me my phone.
- Okay. Hold this.
Vin Diesel is dying, and
I need you to save him.
I don't care how much it costs.
I'll buy every shock exacerbater
in this town if I have to.
Carly, I told you
when we first met,
you shouldn't be
driving this car, okay?
It-it isn't safe.
Why don't you just
get a new one?
Because I...
I just can't, okay?
I can't give up on this car.
I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
- And called me names.
- Yes. Right.
And should've listened
to me from the start.
Oh. True, I know,
that's why I called you.
I am sorry for all those things.
But I am begging
you, Wes, please,
will you save Vin Diesel?
Okay. I will try.
I'm gonna need you
to do more than try.
: Actually,
trying's fine. You do you.
Thank you, Wes.
But do it.
The birds represent capitalism.
And the white woman represents
well, nothing.
- She's just having a bad day.
- Mm-mm.
No birds.
If I can't fly, no one
should be allowed to.
Who's ready for teatime?
Spencer, what are you doing?
Oh, I just thought you
and Dutch might enjoy
a formal tea service.
And you were right. Give me
one of them hot hand towels.
- Ooh.
- Oh, anything for you, Harper,
and your boss, whose voice is
like a classically-trained
instrument
that she should rest,
which is why I brought the tea.
Ooh. No, thank you.
I don't like beverages that
start with the letter "T."
I'm looking at you, tonic water.
Okay. Thank you, Spencer. Bye.
: No!
This look represents
the struggle between...
Me and Spencer, apparently.
What is happening and why?
Oh. I just need to do
a few repairs in here.
Is that disruptive?
Yeah, why don't you just
stop the presentation
and then email the
slides to Dutch.
Who else loves this idea?
I don't.
I would like the
hammering to stop
and for the presentation
to continue but better.
Get out. Now.
: All right. Okay.
Oh, no! Oh!
I guess I should stay
and clean this up.
- Oh.
- How's it going in here?
I spilled the tea.
Oh, Spencer.
Harper, I am so sorry that
I faked my kidnapping,
but at least now you know.
You what?
Oh. You meant...
If you'd let me sing it,
at least you would've
gotten a hit out of it.
It's only been three hours
of waiting on Wes
to fix Vin Diesel.
How did you handle waiting
four years for Maeve?
By doing everything I could
to find that betrayer.
You know what, yeah,
that's a good idea.
Keep busy. Give me
some more ideas.
Okay. I took out ads
in the newspaper,
I made the hashtag
"Save Maeve" go viral,
I even recorded a charity
single that went to number 27
on the iTunes chart for
songs about missing cousins.
I don't want to do any of that.
Okay.
Give it to me straight.
Did he make it?
I did everything I
could, but I'm sorry.
Vin Diesel's gone.
-  Oh, no.
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
- Carly, stay with me.
Just because he's gone
doesn't mean you are, too.
I just can't believe it.
I mean, he was only 50.
We never even got to take
that cross-country
road trip together
that we always talked about.
Uh, hey, I might be
overstepping here,
but could this be about
more than just a car?
It's okay, you can tell me.
Mechanic-client privilege.
My best friend
Sam and I saved up
and bought Vin Diesel together
when I was in college.
She's actually the
one who named him.
We went everywhere in that car.
Road trips to Snoqualmie Falls,
the exotic jerky emporium
over the border in Idaho,
out to the forest to
search for bigfoot.
- Did you ever find him?
- Uh, it's a long story.
: But yes.
A couple years ago,
Sam moved away,
and I just really miss her.
But whenever I'm
inside Vin Diesel, I...
Okay, I'm just gonna say
"my car" from now on.
Driving my car, it just helps
me feel connected to Sam.
I know it sounds silly.
No, it's not.
What's silly is
having a connection
and not appreciating it.
What's silly is lying
to someone for years
and then telling the truth
to your brand-new boyfriend
before your best friend/cousin!
What's silly
is faking your own kidnapping.
Like, who does that?
Maeve, that's who.
Maeve.
So, there's, like, a whole
other thing going on here.
Mind your business.
Anyway, thanks for
trying to save my car.
Uh, here. Let me see.
- How much do I owe you?
- No. Nothing.
Put it toward your new car.
I don't know.
I wasn't really driving a
whole lot lately anyway.
That
gets a little tired.
Uh, well, maybe you
don't need a car.
For example, if you had
a date on Saturday night,
I bet he would be totally
happy to come pick you up.
A hypothetical date?
Well, where is he
hypothetically taking me?
Anywhere you
hypothetically want to go.
I believe it was Sir Edmond
Dellingsworth who said,
- "What is a circle?"
- Boo!
Lose the sheet already.
All right, all right.
I just wanted to say
something with some gravitas.
Behold my latest piece!
Wow.
Is this Vin Diesel?
Yep!
I took Carly's old
car, repainted him,
and turned it into a new Seat
of Sitting for the studio.
Try saying that five times fast.
: New Seat of
Sitting for the studio.
New Seat of Sitting
for the studio.
Yeah, not that hard, dude.
Oh, my God. Spencer,
this is amazing.
Aw.
My car and I had so
many good memories,
and now we get to make more.
Our secret gum
wad's still there.
- Ew.
Sam used this once to keep
our seat belts together.
And another time I used it
to keep my toes apart
after a pedicure.
You know, um, Carly
getting a second chance
with her car is making
me a little jealous.
Oh, 'cause all our
cars got repossessed
when we lost our money.
Well, thanks for ruining
this special moment.
I'm sad now.
No, because she gets
to make more memories.
And I want that for us.
Harper, I am so sorry
I didn't tell you.
I just didn't know how.
If it means anything, "Save
Maeve" was my ringtone.
It was a tastefully
mournful bop.